Hi, Sung-jin.
Surprised?
I wanted to see you
and tell you in person,
but if I did,
I thought I'd go weak.
I...
I'm going back to Berlin.
I don't know.
I'm not sure about...
my relationship with you.
I'm not sure who you are.
So it makes me mad.
I have so many doubts
and worries.
So it torments me.
It's really hard for me now.
I think
I'm not fit to be married.
I shouldn't get married.
I'm a weird girl.
It's not your fault, Sung-jin,
but mine.
So I should go.
Thanks to you, Sung-jin,
I've been so happy.
I hope you're happy too.
Bye.
(Sung-jin, watch the video)
(Hidden Face)
Now, let's begin with
the 1st Movement,
104th bar, the second beat.
One, two, three!
- Maestro.
- Hi, chief.
You don't look too well.
Really?
I have matters to discuss.
It's about the cello section.
We can't keep practicing
with a seat left empty forever.
The balance is off in tutti.
The musicians pretend
they're not worried.
Yeah, I know we should wait
for Su-yeon to come back.
But they're whispering about it,
so I thought I should tell you.
I'll deal with it soon.
You understand, right?
It's Geisha coffee.
- Try it.
- Thank you.
Has it been 12 days?
I think so.
She definitely
didn't go to Berlin.
Her cello is still at home
and she didn't take many clothes.
Don't worry.
She'll crawl back soon
with some lame excuse.
So stupid.
She thinks she can do anything
as the music director's daughter!
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
She must be in a hotel somewhere
enjoying room service now.
It's because I raised her wrong.
I had her when I was young
and let her have
anything she wants.
Or maybe I raised her well,
but she just takes after
my personality.
Anyway, it's all my fault.
It's my fault.
By the way, a cellist is coming
for an interview today.
She's probably in your office now.
- A cellist?
- Yes.
Su-yeon called in a friend
to cover for her.
She is a responsible girl,
you know?
But shouldn't we wait
a few more days?
- You think?
- Yes.
If she returns
and suddenly finds
a replacement, she'll be sad.
Dear.
Didn't you tell the manager
that you can't wait any longer?
You wanted a replacement.
You said the tutti is weaker.
That's true
from a conductor's standpoint.
But tell me things directly.
Don't let me hear it from others.
But director, I...
Interview the cellist.
Is this your profile?
Yes.
I heard you're Su-yeon's friend,
but you guys didn't
go to same school.
(Resume)
We were taught by same teacher.
I see.
And Su-yeon
was an assistant instructor
in my high school.
She said there
would be a spot here
and told me to apply.
Did she mention anything else?
I was surprised to hear from her
after many years.
Did I come by mistake?
No.
Let's hear you play, then.
Actually, my cello is not fit
to be played suddenly.
If it's okay,
could you listen to my recording?
Sure.
Schubert Arpeggione Sonata.
Are you applying for fun
with nothing better to do?
What do you mean?
How can you apply
with an easier piece like this?
I love Schubert the most
because his pieces
are the saddest.
When I listen to his songs,
they're so sad that I feel better.
That's why he is my favorite.
I'll leave my profile.
Please throw it away.
I'll leave the USB, too.
You can delete it and reuse it
or throw it out.
It was nice meeting you,
conductor.
I love Schubert the most
because his pieces
are the saddest.
What are you doing here?
I saw it on your profile.
Did I catch you at a bad time?
I was very disrespectful
earlier today.
I was in a bad mood
from something else.
I took it out on you by mistake.
I came to apologize.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
I enjoyed your performance.
Please join our orchestra.
Really?
Well, I'd love to.
Great.
(Franz Schubert)
It's Schubert.
Yes, it's Schubert.
We'll be performing that.
I guess that settles it.
Please practice and come.
Wait.
Actually,
Schubert is my favorite too,
for the same reason
as yours, Mi-ju.
First of all,
it's such a low-end instrument.
You can hear the difference
from the rest.
Right, director?
She must've practiced a lot,
but she needs more work.
We really needed Su-yeon
at the practice.
I knew we should've waited
for Su-yeon, but the conductor...
What did you think?
How was she during practice?
Well...
It was her first practice.
I'll have to see how she does.
Still, you must have
first impressions of her.
I think she's very hard working.
She played surprisingly well
for not having much prep time.
She has good manner too.
Then, as a conductor,
you don't have any complaints?
That settles it.
He means he's satisfied with her
only as a sub.
Right, maestro?
He says he's satisfied.
Why are you saying that?
She's hardworking
with good manner.
I guess my crazy girl
doesn't have to come back.
Yes, it happens often.
It usually starts
after a few tries,
but it won't now.
Yes.
I'm in Goyang-si.
Pardon?
Can you come any sooner?
Is there a problem?
My car won't start.
I see...
Are you going home?
Yes.
My cello looks so small.
It looked huge in my backseat.
Still, I saw you
squeeze it in well.
I didn't think it'd go in.
When did you see me?
That day, after your interview.
I glanced out the window and saw.
Really?
I'm embarrassed.
Ah...
Would you care for dinner?
That'd be nice.
I like grilling meat, too.
I never grill meat like this.
I have a complex.
A complex?
My mother runs a small restaurant.
If I grill meat well,
they'll think it's because of
my upbringing.
It's raining.
Oh, no. We don't have umbrellas.
But I like the rain.
By the way,
I heard other members say
you two had problems.
Did you fight?
- I heard she left...
- Can we skip that?
I'd rather not say.
By the way,
I have a complex too.
What is it?
I'm an orphan.
When I was in grade 10,
my parents died
in a car accident.
I lost my mom
and my dad at once.
So I have a complex
of being an orphan.
Cheers.
Thank you!
- Thank you. Bye!
- Take care.
Bye.
Shouldn't I sit in the back?
I'm smaller and skinnier.
I said it's okay.
When the driver comes,
I'll ask him to
drop you off first.
When we take the cello out,
I'll go to the front seat.
You said that five times already.
Did I?
Just like the rain,
the alcohol went down smoothly.
I wish I could drink more.
But everything is closed, right?
Mi-ju.
Yes?
Should we go for another drink?
Where?
How about our house?
Actually, I don't know much
about wine.
It looks expensive.
I don't either.
You don't have to humor me.
You must know.
No, I really don't.
I just drink it.
Not only that...
People who describe
wine and coffee in great detail,
I despise them.
They say,
it smells like the dirt of August
or that it contains May's sun.
It's ridiculous.
Jeez.
Well, then.
We don't know, but let's toast.
Cheers.
The house is so nice.
I'm completely drunk.
Wine makes me so drunk.
I'm so dizzy.
Washing my face didn't help.
But I got soaked and drunk.
I'm a mess.
Please don't.
I can't.
We can't do this in this room.
It's wrong.
How will I face her later?
Wait!
I loved it.
Why'd you strip me?
That's poop from a civet
after eating coffee beans.
Amazing, huh?
- I guess.
- It's all in the packaging.
Even poo can be made to look good
and sold at a high price.
It doesn't matter
what it really is.
It's how people see it.
Seeing is believing.
That's why people
need to be packaged well too.
People need packaging, right?
By the way,
it's about Su-yeon.
Don't you think it's strange?
I thought she got the whims again
before getting married.
But something's not right.
Know what's the weirdest part?
She's not using her card.
Su-yeon is the type
to go shopping even if I die.
But she's not using her card.
That's so strange.
Well...
Maybe it's her way of showing
she's really mad?
I mean...
Maybe she wants to stay
completely in hiding?
You think?
I'm slowly
starting to get worried.
She's never been so resolute.
I know...
It rained a lot last night.
That's not my fault.
But the rest was all my fault.
Getting drunk,
going to your house,
and going in your room.
To avoid any more faults,
I won't reply to you.
You understand, right?
(Cello, Kim Mi-ju)
Hello?
Are you there?
Do you think I'm crazy?
I shouldn't come here.
But I came here twice.
Your piano playing made me come.
I'm here twice in her room...
What's wrong?
Hot water suddenly came out
from the shower.
I'm okay.
What?
I'm fine, really.
I didn't get burned.
Really?
Wait outside.
(3 months earlier)
What? This sucks.
I wanted to hug you at the gate.
What's more important than me?
Forget it.
Sung-jin, Mom can't come.
She's sending her driver.
I'll tell him to come here.
We have way too many bags.
It's okay.
Sung-jin!
Can you buy us some coffee?
I can smell it and want it now.
Okay.
Mr. Kim? It's me.
Please come to gate 4.
Thanks!
Wow.
I had no idea
you'd come to the airport.
I wasn't busy,
so I came to give you
the key and welcome you.
No welcoming,
and we agreed you'd
leave the key above the gate.
Here.
About the renovations...
I did my best, but
I don't know if you'll like it.
I saw it all on our video calls.
I made all the choices
and okayed everything.
Of course it's my style.
Why mention something so obvious?
Right.
What's not my style is...
you coming
to meet me here like this.
Isn't this a bit weird?
I guess you're right.
I'm thankful.
Thank you for all that you did,
but what's wrong is wrong.
Right?
I understand.
Oh, coffee! Thank you!
Let's go.
- Do you like it?
- It's huge.
When I took lessons here
as a student,
I thought it was like
a haunted house.
But then it kept coming to mind.
I had it fully renovated.
Like it?
Of course.
We can play loud music
and there's a great yard.
My dream was to live
in a house like this.
It came true without even trying.
Why?
You don't like it?
Yes, I like it.
But I kind of feel awkward
and wonder if I belong here.
Get used to it.
What?
All the things...
that you haven't
experienced before.
You know why?
You're the maestro, Sung-jin.
Maestro...
It's natural for maestros.
Besides, it's nothing for my mom
to give me a house like this.
Don't feel burdened.
It's not that.
I'm just not used to it.
Everything is natural for you.
Understand? Our maestro.
I went here recently.
Is it nice?
It's amazing with a jungle
by the beach.
Really?
Wow!
There's a jungle by the beach.
Sung-jin! Look at this!
Isn't it amazing?
- Don't look at her bikini.
- Hey!
It's beautiful!
It costs $30,000 for 5 nights
so it's a bit much.
But it's worth it.
Su-yeon. Is the wedding
right after the concert?
Yes.
Then it'll be peak season.
It'll be more expensive.
It doesn't matter.
They're good.
Dear.
I can smoke here, right?
Yes, of course.
Why are you doing the dishes?
We need more wine glasses.
It suits you.
By the way,
did your mom say anything
after our meeting?
She loved meeting you.
She said you're so elegant.
She's happy I'm marrying
a great family.
By the way,
my opinion of you changed
after meeting your family.
I had no idea how great you are!
You're very strong-willed
with set goals.
I can sense how hard you work
to build an image for yourself.
Why tell me this?
Just saying what I realized.
Like people say,
you're a self-made man.
I've come to like you more, dear.
I worried about our housewarming.
But it ended grandly, right?
Yes.
Did you like that place?
Where?
The resort in the pictures.
I loved it.
You said you'd decide that.
You don't look too happy.
Is it because of
what my friends said?
About what?
That they were surprised
that I chased you.
They hinted that you approached me
for obvious reasons.
I didn't care at all.
Really?
Okay.
Then I'll decide on that resort.
$30,000 for 5 nights, huh?
Expensive?
Who cares?
Mom is paying anyway!
You know what?
Babe, do you want to know
what I can't stand?
Like being sarcastic.
I want nothing but the best.
Having the most luxurious
and comfortable stuff is my style.
I hate it when people rebuke
and make sarcastic
remarks on that.
Let's fix that, okay?
Okay.
Fine. Sleep first.
Wait!
You forgot to kiss me.
Thanks.
What do you think?
He's getting better, huh?
I think
he's finally getting adjusted.
Come on.
Let's compliment him
properly, Madam director.
Whatever.
Take a look at this.
(Concert Plan)
The planning team suggested this.
Let's decide together.
Oh, please.
He strongly insists the opening be
'The Unfinished Symphony.'
Let him have that.
Then let's go with
more lyrical pieces.
This was a concert in Vienna.
It's a good example.
Right? Of course.
It was very successful.
We should change the opening too.
I agree.
By the way,
what did you talk about
with that violinist?
What violinist?
On the stage, was it In-jung?
You seemed to be talking about
something funny.
We were?
She held her hand out
and you kindly looked at it.
Oh, that.
She said her nails were weak
and kept breaking off.
What's wrong?
What?
Ever since we came back to Seoul.
What are you talking about?
You're nice to the violinist
and everyone else,
but why are you cold to me?
You quip about everything I do
or show no interest.
Why?
Hmm?
Can I say something too?
What?
Why do you keep embarrassing me?
- Who?
- Me?
Must you two have a meeting
while the musicians watched?
Huh?
Must you make sure they know
that I'm a puppet?
Mom just wanted my opinion
before deciding with you.
Exactly!
Why talk about that
where everyone can see you?
What?
Is that so embarrassing?
Think I'd be proud
to be a puppet?
You're wearing the bracelet.
I'm sorry for going overboard
at the airport.
I apologize.
I understand.
Why didn't you come to
the housewarming?
You didn't invite me.
I must be losing it.
I thought I did!
It's so like you.
You're so cool.
I love that you're always
so cool and calm.
Sung-jin drives me nuts.
He's handsome
and is a promising conductor.
His family is poor,
but that doesn't matter.
One thing bothers me.
What?
I don't think he likes me.
But you like him?
Are you crazy?
But he has to like me.
Even if I don't like him,
he must like me.
It's only fair.
How is that fair?
It is!
So you came to me for advice?
Mi-ju.
Remember?
That day when I first kissed you?
Where was it?
The cold room at Ms. Park's house.
I've never liked anyone else
but you since then.
You too, right?
It may seem like
I'm betraying you...
No, I am betraying you.
Still, I'll never betray
our memories together.
I hope you know that.
Okay.
Good.
Did you go inside the cold room?
Yes.
Then you must have the key.
This is how you decorated it?
- It's nice.
- Jeez.
Who cares if it's nice,
we don't get along.
Come with me.
You brought the key, right?
Okay.
Do you have to do this?
It's because he makes me mad.
I practically saved him.
He was dying with no work
and no money.
How dare he play hard to get?
I'll teach him a lesson
before we get married.
He thinks my generosity
is his right!
I hate that word the most.
What? Generosity?
Anyway,
I want to see what he does
without me.
It's going to be fun!
It's here, right?
Come over here.
You're really going in there?
Push it.
Whoa.
Open it.
Wow.
It's cold.
It's the same as before.
Doesn't this bring back memories?
Su-yeon.
I'm scared in here.
Silly? Why are you scared?
I'm here. Don't be.
When I give you a sign like this,
come in here and wait for me.
Okay?
Like your underling?
Like an underling and a slave.
You like me, right?
Then you're my slave.
Got it?
Then kiss me.
Oh, please.
You said you like me.
Okay, then close your eyes.
Okay, fine.
I'm closing my eyes.
I think
I'm not fit to be married.
I shouldn't get married.
It's not your fault, Sung-jin,
but mine.
So I should go.
Thanks to you, Sung-jin,
I've been so happy.
Wasn't that tear-jerking?
I know it.
He's going to break down
when he sees this.
He'll be so sad.
It's so sad.
(Sung-jin, watch the video)
Is this too much? No, it's cold.
So the opening song
is a Schubert?
Yes!
You know how much he insisted?
He says Schubert is the saddest.
He loves Schubert.
Wait! I should mess it up
like I left in a rush.
He said it's so sad,
he feels better.
Packed everything?
Yes.
Good.
It's heavy.
Give me the key.
How long will you stay?
Maybe 3 days at most.
I have to practice.
It'll help me diet too.
I'm going in.
Slide the bookcase back.
Su-yeon.
I'll go now.
Bye!
(No signal)
Hi, Sung-jin.
Surprised?
I'm going back to Berlin.
I don't know.
Oh, you're so sad.
I'm not sure about
my relationship with you.
I'm not sure who you are.
So it makes me mad.
I have so many doubts
and worries.
Untie me, please.
I won't do it again.
Let me go. Please?
Jeez.
He's so sad. The poor thing.
Let's see.
Sung-jin! I'm here.
Sung-jin! I'm in here!
Sung-jin!
Look! I'm in here!
I'm stuck here!
Hey!
Sung-jin! I'm in here!
Sung-jin! I'm stuck in here!
Sung-jin!
Come back!
Damn it!
Dammit.
(Beef flavor noodles)
Why'd you come so late?
I thought I'd be stuck forever.
Are you doing okay?
You...
How'd you come in here?
Why are you at our house?
I'm drunk.
Sung-jin got me drunk.
I said I couldn't drink wine,
but he kept giving it to me.
I think he wants me.
Are you crazy?
The key...
I switched it.
To play a trick on you.
You must be angry
and shocked.
Should I let you out?
But if I do, will you forgive me?
You will forgive?
Then I'd better do something
unforgiveable.
What?
What is this!
Mi-ju...
I'm completely drunk.
- Wine makes me so drunk.
- Sung-jin...
What are you doing?
Mi-ju!
Don't do it! This isn't funny!
Mi-ju.
Please don't.
Hey!
Don't do this! Stop!
Mi-ju! You hate men touching you!
Don't do it!
Stop! Don't touch her there!
Stop! Mi-ju!
Stop!
Good.
That's it.
Stop! Are you crazy!
You're insane!
Mi-ju! Stop it!
Sung-jin.
Are you crazy!
Why'd you strip me?
Stop it!
No!
Stop it! Stop!
Stop!
Don't do it!
No...
(7 months earlier)
(Going well / So tired)
(I miss you)
I thought you girls
hated this house.
Why Ms. Park?
I was so harsh on you girls
when you took lessons here.
Thanks to that,
we make a living off the cello.
I'm glad Su-yeon
bought this house from me.
This is almost the same.
Yes.
The bookcase is so pretty.
Did you leave things the same
in there?
Pardon?
You thought I didn't know?
I knew since you two started
going in there.
I'm sorry.
For what? No need.
I thought you two were just
fooling around like kids.
But you stayed together for years
and bought a house like this.
What is this place?
I've always wondered.
My late father added this
when the house was built.
My father
was in that bad unit 731,
during the Japanese
colonial period.
He was a medical officer there.
I see.
He did some bad things there.
So he was always scared
and wanted to stay in hiding.
After work, he'd go in here
and watch Mom,
me and my sister
through the mirrors.
He'd call us in and lock the chain
around us too.
Is the chain still there?
What?
How do you feel?
Good.
It feels so cool and thrilling.
I wanted to try it.
Give me the key.
What? Why'd you do that?
You can get it and untie me.
What if I don't?
I know you'll untie me.
I trust you.
You trust me?
Yes.
I trust only you.
I'm not going to untie you.
No, I know you'll untie me
because I'm yours.
(She)
Howdie!
Hi. What are you up to?
I was taking a video
to show you the finished house.
You did a great job.
By the way,
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I'm returning to Korea
with someone.
Who?
A man.
He's my fiance.
I met him here.
We're going back together.
Wow.
I know.
Wow, right?
Wow...
What about me?
I know.
'I know?'
Congratulate me?
I'm getting married.
I'll be living with a man.
Now, I'll live my real life
that people recognize.
Real life?
I'll live my real life
from now on.
If you'll live your real life
from now on,
what about me?
Was I a fake life to you?
Come on.
Let me be honest with you.
You know where I'm sensitive
and love to be touched.
You're like my tool and I'm yours.
We knew that didn't we?
Let's not sob over this, okay?
And...
Do you think I'm crazy?
I shouldn't come here.
But I came here twice.
You'll throw me...
in jail when you
come out, won't you?
No! I won't!
I swear I won't!
I hurt you first.
I won't blame you for anything.
I won't report you.
So, please let me out!
I guess I deserve it.
By the way,
I finally understand
what you meant.
The real life...
It's the life that
people think is real
and normal, right?
I understand now.
And...
I think
I need that life too.
What are you talking about?
I'll have that man
for a real life.
I'll live it.
What?
Sorry Su-yeon.
You'll have to keep staying
inside there.
Mi-ju! No!
Mi-ju! I was wrong!
It's all my fault! Don't do this!
What's wrong?
Hot water suddenly came out
from the shower.
- What?
- I'm okay.
I'm fine, really.
I didn't get burned.
- Really?
- Wait outside.
Okay.
We have to cut through the wall
along this pipe.
Or I can kill the
original water line
and connect a new one.
That's a big job too,
but it's better.
This house is like a bunker.
The walls are so thick.
Here! Over here!
There's someone in here!
Kill the original pipe?
No! No!
If that's the best way,
let's do it.
When can you start?
I'll start right away.
No! Stop! No!
Wait.
Do you hear that wooing sound?
No! Stop! Don't!
What the heck!
Jeez!
This is creepy. I'm leaving.
Sung-jin! I did it! It was me!
It's so weird!
There's no record
of her flying out.
She's not abroad.
She never used her credit card.
Her phone is still off.
She never called me once!
I'm her mom.
I know my daughter.
This is so unlike Su-yeon.
Something must be wrong.
She's not the type to be ghosting
for no reason.
Right, dear?
Don't you agree?
I do.
So,
I reported her missing.
I should've done it days ago.
The police will go
to your house tomorrow.
Our house?
Don't get me wrong.
It's not because I suspect you.
They're just going to check.
Director.
Are you suspecting me?
No, of course not.
Don't work so half-heartedly.
Public servants...
What is he looking for
half-heartedly?
The corpse that I buried?
Don't take it personally.
We're just following orders here.
Actually, our job is to observe
your face as we run the search.
See your expression.
So, how is my expression?
Bright, clean and innocent.
Don't mind the size.
It's too stuffy and small, right?
I like smaller homes.
Our house is way too big.
I don't like hearing that.
'Our house.'
1117.
That's your door code?
What about it?
Su-yeon's birthday
is November 17th.
Oh, really?
I'm just using the same code
the previous owner set.
What a coincidence
that it's her birthday.
I don't know how to change
things like that.
Yes?
Look at this.
Director. I saw this a hundred...
Look at it again.
See?
Right here.
Look at the mirror behind Su-yeon.
In the mirror,
see someone else's hand there?
I only looked at Su-yeon's face
when I played this,
but I got a strange feeling today
and looked closely.
Then I saw the hand. See it?
Yes.
Someone was with her
when she left home.
What brings you here?
You suddenly missed me?
Yes.
How romantic.
Don't ring the bell.
Just press 1117 and come in.
There's no one really
who is being difficult.
They're all nice and good to me.
I've especially gotten close
with the cello team.
I went out for lunch
with the first cellist.
She's so nice.
How can she bow so strongly
and charismatically?
I want to learn that from her.
Wait.
There is one person.
The concertmaster.
You know his personality.
The wind section makes mistakes,
but he yells
at the string section.
I think our orchestra will be
much better off without him.
Why aren't you eating?
I have a question.
What is it?
You were with Su-yeon
when she left, weren't you?
What do you mean?
Your wrist was reflected
in the mirror.
That bracelet...
The one with the blue stones.
You're not wearing it today.
Blue stones?
This bracelet?
Yes.
I was in the room
the day she left.
What?
You lied about everything?
You said she called you in years
and you two aren't close.
You said you've never been
to our house.
They were all lies.
I'm sorry.
But can you stop saying,
'our house?'
What?
What do you want?
Why'd you lie to me?
Because Su-yeon told me to.
She told me to renovate, so I did.
She asked to help her leave
the house, so I did.
She said to fill-in for her,
so I did.
I just did what she told me to.
You do whatever she says?
Are you her servant?
Or her slave?
Am I really a slave?
The only thing I decided
and did was sleeping with you.
Where's Su-yeon now?
You must know.
I have no idea.
Don't lie.
You two are a couple, aren't you?
What do you mean?
I saw the pictures in here
of you two.
What are you talking about?
Come on.
We were just goofing around.
It's just a sign
of our friendship.
Stop lying.
Tell me.
Where's Su-yeon now?
I seriously don't know.
I swear I don't know.
Don't kill the water line!
It's me!
It's me.
Turn it on.
Okay, I will!
It's me! I'm here!
See? Over here.
I'm in here!
Su-yeon, is that you?
Turn it off.
Su-yeon.
Are you inside the house?
I'm in here.
Are you locked up?
I'm stuck!
Get me out of here, Sung-jin!
Su-yeon?
Are you in here?
Su-yeon...
I'm here! Sung-jin!
I'm right in front of you!
Over here!
I'm trapped in here!
Su-yeon? Are you here?
I'm stuck inside here!
You're in there, aren't you?
Yes! Yes!
What's wrong?
Why'd you stop?
What is it?
Then you saw everything.
Right?
You saw me with Mi-ju...
You saw everything.
I don't care. Let me out.
It's okay! I don't care!
Just get me out of here!
That means...
Mi-ju knew and came here, right?
She wanted to show you on purpose.
Right?
She knew you were watching.
I don't care! I swear!
Damn it.
What are you two?
Save me! Sung-jin!
Please get me out of here!
Please!
Please get me out!
Please help me!
It's Su-yeon's fault.
She just used and insulted me.
You locked her up for that?
I didn't lock her up.
She went in on her own.
Then something went wrong.
All I did was not let her out.
It's the same thing!
It's different.
Locking her is a crime.
Bringing her out is a question
of generosity.
There's no generosity
left in me for her now.
She's an evil person.
She just uses people
then abandons them.
What do you plan to do?
Just keep her in there?
What if she starves to death?
I'm surprised she didn't.
She has no food.
Mi-ju.
This is like murder.
No!
It is murder!
Then what?
Let her out now?
Then apologize
and say it was a joke?
Think she'll just forgive me
and say it's her fault too?
- Still, this is wrong.
- You know her personality.
She'll throw both of us in prison
as accomplices.
Isn't that why you came to me?
Because you're scared?
If not, you would've called
the cops or contractors
and got her out.
Then what?
Just leave her there
till she dies?
I'm not sure either.
But
I feel relieved that you know.
You decide.
I'll follow you.
No matter what.
I know you won't forgive me.
After everything
I did to get here...
When you come out,
you'll destroy me.
You'll crush me to pieces,
won't you?
That's what Shin Su-yeon would do,
of course.
But Su-yeon,
you lied to me too.
You love women.
Right?
Bravo! Bravo!
Today's full rehearsal
was fantastic!
We still need to work out
a few things.
Have a seat.
I was so impressed.
I thought it was concert day!
But why do you look so gloomy?
Me?
Are you hiding something from me?
Of course not.
Have you heard anything
on Su-yeon?
No.
Oh, my.
We're finally working
hand in glove,
but it's a dilemma.
Think about Su-yeon.
She left her fiance,
but her mom keeps him employed.
I mean appointed.
Then it'll be hard for her
to come back.
It dawned on me.
If Su-yeon keeps staying away,
I'm not sure
what to make of our relationship.
Understand?
But it was really good today.
(Su-yeon)
(It's me)
(Are you two getting along well
while I'm gone?)
- What are you going to do?
- Mi-ju.
Let's think rationally.
If she's still alive, it means
we didn't commit a crime.
Maybe for you,
but
it's a crime for me.
Still, it's better than murder!
I checked.
The key is still in my bag.
Actually, I suspected it was you.
Me?
Yes.
Come on.
Let's just stay like this.
It's not easy to get out of there.
Let's calm down.
No.
Go and open it now.
Or else I'll call the cops.
Maestro called.
Something urgent came up.
He cancelled today's practice.
One more thing,
cellist Kim Mi-ju called
and said
she's sick and went to a doctor.
That is all.
Thank you.
This is so scary!
Director, can you believe this?
After getting the texts,
they'll run here
if they're innocent.
If they're guilty,
they won't show.
With a copy of her ID,
her legal representative
can activate her number on
another phone.
They don't know that.
They must've panicked.
I'm so scared.
What the hell did they do?
I'm terrified.
This is the entrance?
There's something behind here?
How do you open this?
Sung-jin.
She can't come out.
How do you open it?
She can't come out of there!
Mi-ju!
Su-yeon?
Are you okay?
See?
I told you she can't come out.
Then who sent those texts?
Su-yeon.
Are you okay?
She's still alive.
Su-yeon.
Su-yeon. Wake up.
Su-yeon!
Su-yeon! Stop it!
Su-yeon! Stop!
Are you crazy?
- Let go.
- Let's get out.
Move.
- Sung-jin! Let's go.
- Move!
She's crazy!
We have to get out!
I said move!
Su-yeon...
Get up.
Are you okay?
Let's go, Sung-jin.
I'll take care of it.
Wash up and eat something.
I'll go to the police.
No.
Don't.
I'm hungry.
Order me some food.
Kimchi stew.
Sure.
I'll take a shower first.
I was dying to take a shower.
Help. Pull this off me.
Mi-ju.
You're on the other side,
aren't you?
I'm taking a hot shower now.
If you mess with the water
like me, you'll pay.
I won't give you water.
Let's talk about the rest
after I shower.
I was worried
because you didn't take my calls.
Then you suddenly come like this
to pay the balance.
It's so like you.
Is Mi-ju doing well?
You knew, didn't you?
About you two?
Of course! I was your teacher.
Things got awkward between us
as I got engaged.
Still,
I plan to keep my ties to her.
We can't lose people, right?
For many years, I thought
your possessive instinct
can't be beat.
You got everything in the end.
Even my house became yours.
I guess you're right.
But Ms. Park?
Did you speak ill of me to Mi-ju?
That I just use
and abandon people?
But I really liked you.
The flowers are so beautiful!
By the way, I love your house.
I'm so happy there.
It's a house that brings
true happiness.
Going golfing?
Sorry. Did I wake you?
It's okay.
I should get up.
You're really into golfing, huh?
It's fun.
Mom says we'll go golfing together
next week.
Yeah, I heard.
Go back to sleep
I'll see you later.
Have fun golfing.
Did you lock it?
Throw the key.
You're dressed so pretty.
Were you waiting for me?
Undress me.
(Hidden Face)
(Directed by Kim Dae-woo)
(Song Seung-heon)
(Cho Yeo Jeong)
(Park Ji-hyun)
(Park Ji-young, Park Sung-guen)